Finding Aid for the Edward Huntsman-Trout Papers LSC.1186
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Client
  - Client: Helms Bakeries, Los Angeles. Photographs., 3 items. (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Client: Hempstead., Residence., April 1957-March 1958; 5 items. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Client: Hersh., Residence., January 1949; 2 items. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Client: Hertz., Garden., February 1946-August 1947; 15 items. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Client: Hill., Residence., October 1937; 2 items. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Client: Hodgson., Residence., February 1952; 1 item. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Client: Hollywood Bowl. Photographs., 5 items. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Client: Hollywood Turf Club, Inglewood [Hollywood Park]., October 1936-January 1938.; 14 items. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Client: Hollywood Turf Club, Inglewood [Hollywood Park] (photos, envelope, sketch)., 3 items. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Client: Holmes., Residence., January-June 1952; 5 items. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Client: Holt. Garden - photograph., 1 item. (Box 133)
  - Client: Holt. Mounted small photographs., 4 items. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Client: Hook, W.R., Bathroom., July 1965; 1 item. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Client: Hook, W.S., Residence., March-October 1923; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Client: Hook, W.S. Residence - photographs., 13 items. (Box 132)
  - Client: Hook, W.S. Mounted small photographs., 3 items. (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Client: Hooks. Correspondence., 1 item. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Client: Hooks., Residence., May 1958; 5 items. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Client: Horn., Correspondence., May 1951; 3 items. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Client: Horton. (Box 104)
  - Client: Horton, J., Grounds., October 1958-????; 4 items. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Client: Horton, J., Grounds., December 1961; 4 items. (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Client: Horton, Joseph., Correspondence, invoices., March 1969-August 1972; 42 items. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Client: Horton, W., Residence., February 1952-March 1955; 4 items. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Client: House with turret, under construction. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Client: House, beginning landscaping. Photographs., 3 items. (Box 38, Folder 47)
  - Client: House, front landscaping. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Client: House, garden. Photographs., 5 items. (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Client: House, hills. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 39)
  - Client: House, landscape. Photographs., 4 items. (Box 38, Folder 51)
  - Client: House, porch construction. Photographs., 3 items. (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Client: House, street, jacaranda trees. Photographs., 4 items. (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Client: Houses, California mountains(?). Photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Client: Hubbard, Henry V., Huntsman-Trout ASLA fellow certificate., 1933 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Client: Hummell., Residence., November 1962-June 1963; 11 item. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Client: Hunter., Residence., January-April 1958; 7 items. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Alterations., August 1929; 2 items. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Family(?) Photograph., 1905 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Engravings - various subjects. (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Tissue sketches., 12 items. (Box __)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Residence., 4 items. (Box 137)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Photostats, Requa leaves collected. (Box 142)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Planting notes., n.d.; 8 items. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Planting lists. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Correspondence, Norman Cousins., 1973; 2 items. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Correspondence, ASLA., January 1970-April 1973; 7 items. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., ASLA rosters, etc., 1973-1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Licenses, legal specs. (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Maps collected (folder 1 of 2). (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Maps collected (folder 2 of 2). (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Postcards collected (England). (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Catalogs, garden items. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Printed envelopes. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., UCLA Extension course, notes., 1946; 68 items. (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. UCLA Extension course, syllabi. (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. UCLA Extension course, exams. (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Correspondence, Garrett Eckbo., March 1966, April-June 1967; 4 items. (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Letters from Michael Laurie., March 1966, June 1967; 3 items. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Correspondence, UC Berkeley., September 1966-May 1967; 9 items. (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Letter from Allen G. Siple., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. In praise of...., ephemera. (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. In praise of the commonplace., 21 item. (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. In praise of the commonplace., 10 items. (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. In praise of the commonplace, 2 copies., 28 items. (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Correspondence, David Streatfield., 1967, 1970-1971, 1973; 14 items. (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Correspondence., 1925-1971; 26 items. (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Bookplates. (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Certificate, State Board., 1954; 1 item. (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Carpentry specifications., February 1937; 21 item. (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. (?) Client log., 1920s-1970s; 1 item. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Client log (photocopy). (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., ASLA member certificate., 1920; 1 item. (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., ASLA fellow certificate., 1933; 1 item. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. (?) Patio notes. Typescript.(6 [1])., 1926; 7 items. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Letter to Ralph Cornell., March 8, 1926; 1 item. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Another room in the home., June 1928; 2 items. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Letter from Fletcher Steele., August 1941; 2 items. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. (?) Daily landscape record (Steele)., 1910s (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Landscape architecture theory., 1 item. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Arnold Arboretum plant notes., 1916 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. (?) Daily landscape record., 1920s (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Statement of professional practice., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., The education of a landscape arch., July 2, 1937; 2 items. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Correspondence with Garrett Eckbo., 1956-1957, n.d.; 4 items. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Art and nature, correspondence., August-December 1959; 17 items. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Art and nature, printed material. (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Art and nature, drafts., 29 items. (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Art and nature, manuscript., 18 items. (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Art and nature, manuscript copies., 72 items. (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout., Commonplace notes., 1945; 2 items. (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Plant lists, California., 4 items. (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Landscape notes, for lecture(?)., 12 items. (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. The world we live in....(3 copies)., 12 items. (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Memorabilia (membership card, etc.)., 4 items. (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Etchings, travel scenes., 8 items. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Etchings, California and miscellaneous., 4 items. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Etchings, Griffith Park planetarium., 8 items. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Sketches, Griffith Park planetarium., 2 items. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Sketches, drawings, miscellaneous., 9 items. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Landscape publications. (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Susan Gross thesis. (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Unidentified projects, etc. (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Photographs, Seville gardens(?)., 5 items. (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Glass slides., 16 items. (Box 41)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Unprocessed negatives, slides, etc. (Box 42)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Architectural drawings., 8 items. (Box 51)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Residence(?)., 17 items. (Box 66)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Charcoal sketches., 9 items. (Box 80)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. (Box 91)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. (Box 93)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout. Site plan (photograph). (Box 98)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout(?). Planting lists (spiral notebook). (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout [and clients]. Engineering specs. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout, Beatrice., Letter from Vera Cornell, etc., n.d.; 5 items. (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Client: Huntsman-Trout(?). Early drawings, plans (inact. mold). (Box 98)
  - Client: Ice Capades, Los Angeles., December 1952.; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Client: Ice Capades, Los Angeles., Correspondence, photograph., December 1952; 2 items. (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Client: Ince. Ranch - photographs., 6 items. (Box 132)
  - Client: Ince., Ranch., September 1923; 2 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Ince. Mounted small photographs., 5 items. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Client: Inch., Residence., January 1968-February 1969; 11 item. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Client: Inch., Residence - also 3 clips., March 1968-July 1969; 3 items. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Client: Inthewoods, Carmel. Mounted small photographs., 8 items. (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Client: Inthewoods, Carmel. Mounted small photographs., 5 items. (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Client: Inthewoods, Carmel. Photographs., 2 items. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Client: Inthewoods, Carmel. Photograph., 1 item. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Client: Irvin., Residence., April 1950-July 1951; 25 items. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Client: Jamison, F.W. Engraving of house (photograph)., 1 item. (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Client: Jamison, F.W. Drawing of fountain (photostat)., 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Client: Job no.1219., 3 items. (Box 49)
  - Client: Johnson. (Box 105)
  - Client: Johnson, Eric., Correspondence, invoices, specs., January 1974-May 1974; 16 items. (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Client: Johnson, H., Residence., November 1930-May 1931; 37 items. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Client: Johnson, H., Garden., September 1930; 4 items. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Client: Johnson, H. Residence., 1 item. (Box 61)
  - Client: Johnson, Harry P. (Box 93)
  - Client: Johnson, R., Garden., December 1949; 1 item. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Client: Johnston., Residence., September 1969-January 1970; 7 items. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Client: Johnston., Residence., January-December 1970; 7 items. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Client: Johnston., Accounts., April-August 1970; 11 item. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Client: Jonsson., Grounds., January 1962; 1 item. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Client: Jordan., Garden., July-November 1928; 4 items. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Client: Kahn., Garden., June 1947-May 1948; 7 items. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Client: Kalin., Correspondence., September 1948; 3 items. (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Client: Kaller., April-July 1957.; 8 items. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Client: Kanter., Grounds., March-July 1959; 6 items. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Client: Kantzler, Jr., Grounds., October 1962-April 1963; 3 items. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Client: Kantzler, Jr. Residence., 4 items. (Box 55)
  - Client: Kaufman., Court., August 1939; 1 item. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Client: Kaufman. (Box 109)
  - Client: Kaufman, Edmund M., Correspondence, invoices (folder 1 of 3)., November 1970-March 1971, n.d.; 31 item. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Client: Kaufman, Edmund M., Correspondence, invoices (folder 2 of 3)., March 1971-September 1972; 99 items. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Client: Kaufman, Edmund M., Invoices (folder 3 of 3)., December 1973-June 1974; 13 items. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Client: Kech. (Box 121)
  - Client: Keck, Mrs. William II., Correspondence, invoices, spec., February 1973-June 1974; 28 items. (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Client: Kerkhoff., June 1931.; 1 item. (Box 138)
  - Client: Kerry. Mounted small photographs., 3 items. (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Client: Killingsworth., Residence., April 1952-October 1954; 5 items. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Client: Kimberly., Garden., March 1929; 1 item. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Client: Kirshner., Additions., November 1963-December 1963; 7 items. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Client: Knapp. Mounted photograph., 1 item. (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Client: Knapp. Mounted photograph., 1 item. (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Client: Knopf., Garden., November 1945; 3 items. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Client: Kozmetsky. Residence., 4 items. (Box 58)
  - Client: Kozmetzky., Residence., November 1962-June 1963; 4 items. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Client: Krueger., Residence., October 1961-April 1962; 4 items. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Client: Krueger. Residence., 7 items. (Box 62)
  - Client: Kunin., Grounds., December 1948-May 1949; 3 items. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Client: La Canada Presbyterian Church, La Canada., August-October 1956.; 11 item. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Client: La Quinta Hotel, Indio., July 1927-January 1928.; 4 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: Lafayette Park, Los Angeles., August 1950-April 1953.; 12 items. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Client: Laguna Colony Club., 3 items. (Box 60)
  - Client: Lake., Residence., January-April 1952; 3 items. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Client: Lakeridge Estates, Hollywood., February 1956.; 8 items. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Client: Lakewood., Playground., July-August 1947; 7 items. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Client: Landau., Residence., July 1936-May 1937; 21 item. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Client: Landscaping, road contruction. Photographs (very small). (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Client: Lang., Residence., December 1950-January 1951; 7 items. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Client: Langworthy., Residence., September-December 1950; 2 items. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Client: Larson., Residence., July-August 1951; 5 items. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Client: Lasky., Residence., January-May 1950; 5 items. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Client: Latchford Marble Glass Company, Los Angeles., September 1953.; 1 item. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Client: Laughlin., Residence., December 1958; 4 items. (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Client: Laurie, Michael. Letters to Huntsman-Trout. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Client: Lederer., Residence., April 1936; 1 item. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Client: Leimert Park, Los Angeles., December 1927.; 1 item. (Box 138)
  - Client: Lewin., Garden., August 1945; 3 items. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Client: Lewis., Grounds., June-July 1970; 2 items. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Client: Lewis., Correspondence, accounts., June-October 1970; 9 items. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Client: Licht, Louis. (Box 111)
  - Client: Licht, Louis., Correspondence, invoices, specifications., September 1972-October 1973; 89 items. (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Client: Lippe, Jerome S., Boundary survey., August 6, 1973; 1 item. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Client: Lipps, Jerome S. (Box 119)
  - Client: Little., Residence., June 1947-February 1955; 6 items. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Client: Livingston., Residence., January-November 1958; 10 items. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Client: Livingstone., Residence., March-July 1954; 3 items. (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Client: Los Angeles parkway map., 1951.; 1 item. (Box 76)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Hugo Reid adobe., 2 items. (Box __)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Topographic., 1 item. (Box __)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Entrance. (Box 106)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. (Box 113)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Enterance. (Box 121)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Topographic., 1 item. (Box 136)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Sprinkler system., 1 item. (Box 136)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Hugo Reid adobe., 4 items. (Box 136)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Sprinkler system., 2 items. (Box 136)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Topographic., 1 item. (Box 136)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Topographic., 3 items. (Box 136)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Entrance., 1 item. (Box 137)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Topographic., 1 item. (Box 137)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum., Garden details., September 1953-March 1961; 28 items. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum., Administration building., November 1953-January 1962; 21 item. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum., Administration building., January 1952-June 1955; 9 items. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum., Tropical plant house., January 1958-January 1962; 5 items. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum., Tropical plant house., 8 items. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum., Hugo Reid adobe correspondence (183 pieces)., October 1954-March 1960 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum., Historical buildings., August 1954-October 1959; 21 item. (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum., Lux., April 1959; 2 items. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum., LASCA house., December 1962-May 1963; 7 items. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum., Entrance development, phase 1., 1960 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum., Entrance development, phase 1., 1962 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Entrance development plan (photo). (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum., Letter to Sandy Turner., May 12, 1972; 1 item. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Report, inscribed by Ralph Cornell. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Gateway walls specifications. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Entranceway plan (photograph)., 1 item. (Box 38, Folder 56)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Photographs., 6 items. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Photographs., 33 items. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Photographs., 1 item. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Miscellaneous., 7 items. (Box 45)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Hugo Reid adobe., 3 items. (Box 46)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Topographic., 1 item. (Box 50)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Topographic., 1 item. (Box 57)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Lux., 7 items. (Box 65)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Greenhouse., 7 items. (Box 70)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Entrance pool., 15 items. (Box 72)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Herb garden., 1 item. (Box 73)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Service building [coach barn]., 18 items. (Box 74)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Carriage house., 3 items. (Box 75)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Pools., 1 item. (Box 82)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Entrance., 6 items. (Box 84)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Entrance., 1 item. (Box 85)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Historical mall., 3 items. (Box 88)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Queen Anne Cottage., 1 item. (Box 89)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. Entrance final. (Box 95)
  - Client: Los Angeles State and County Arboretum. (Box 97)
  - Client: Lucas. Residence., 3 items. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Client: Lux Arboretum, Monrovia. Master plan. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Client: Lynch., Grounds., May 1952-August 1958; 8 items. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Client: Lynch., Accounts and correspondence., April-August 1952; 4 items. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Client: Malinow., Residence., June 1948; 2 items. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Client: Mandeville Canyon topographical. (Box 90)
  - Client: Manella., Grounds., May-June 1967; 1 item. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Client: Mankowski., Residence., January 1926-January 1927; 6 items. (Box 139)
  - Client: Mannick., Grounds., May 1965; 3 items. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Client: Marquez Avenue School, Pacific Palisades., October-December 1955.; 15 items. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Client: Martin., Residence., September 1928-February 1931; 35 items. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Client: Martin. Study (photograph)., 1 item. (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Client: Martin. Plan (Mott photograph and negative)., 2 items. (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Client: Martin. Folio (ephemera)., 1 item. (Box 133)
  - Client: Martin. Residence - photographs., 5 items. (Box 133)
  - Client: Martin. Residence., 2 items. (Box 141)
  - Client: Maxwell., Residence., March 1952-June 1953; 16 items. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Client: Mayhew., Residence., December 1950-January 1951; 6 items. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Client: McAllister., Residence., October 1939-June 1940; 14 items. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Client: McCarty., Residence., November 1925; 2 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: McCarty., Mounted small photograph., October 1925; 1 item. (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Client: McCarty., Mounted small photographs., December 12, 1925; 9 items. (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Client: McCarty(?). Mounted small photographs., 5 items. (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Client: McCarty(?). Mounted small photographs., 2 items. (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Client: McClure., Residence., August 1936-May 1937; 15 items. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Client: McClure. Residence., 15 items. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Client: McCreery., Residence., September 1955-March 1956; 17 items. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Client: McCulloch., Residence., June 1968-October 1969; 8 items. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Client: McCulloch, R.P. (Box 93)
  - Client: McLaghlen. Residence - photographs of plan(s)., 3 items. (Box 133)
  - Client: McLaughlin., Residence., June-October 1926; 2 items. (Box 138)
  - Client: McLuke., 3 items. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Client: McNabb., Playhouse., January-March 1946; 11 item. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Client: McNaghten., Residence (Bing Crosby)., May-July 1932; 11 item. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Client: McNaghten., Residence., August 1932-October 1944; 17 items. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Client: McNaghten., Additions., April-August 1953; 13 items. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Client: McNaghten. Pool specifications., 35 items. (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Client: McNaghten, Malcolm. Photograph., 1 item. (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Client: McNaghten, Malcolm (Bing Crosby). Photographs., 6 items. (Box 133)
  - Client: McNaghten, Malcolm(?). Photograph -Maynard L. Parker., 1 item. (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Client: McNaghten(?). Photographs., 6 items. (Box 38, Folder 4)